A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants Them-Tw FA732H FA732H
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - Them to Tw, 1937-2006
  - Tve Television Trust for the Environment (09451291), 1994 September 01-1995 August 31 (Reel R7749)
    SUPPORT FOR CHINESE WOMEN'S FILM PROJECT
  - Tve Television Trust for the Environment (10000729), 2000 March 01-2001 December 31 (Reel R8856)
    SUPPORT FOR THE PRODUCTION AND DISSEMINATION OF A REPORT AND A SERIES OF FILMS FOR INTERNATIONAL BROADCAST ON PALESTINIAN REFUGEES IN THE CONTEXT OF FINAL STATUS DISCUSSIONS
    Middle East and North Africa (Cairo);PSJ - Office of the Vice President;Human Rights;Media Arts and Culture
    Azzam, Fatih Samih;Higashi, Taryn;Santos, John Phillip
    Middle East; Refugees--Legal status, laws etc.; Refugees--Middle East; Palestinian Arabs
  - Tver Fund for Legal Training Support "Lawyer" (09900490), 1999 February 01-2002 June 30 (Reel R9025)
    DEVELOPMENT OF A LAW CLINIC AND RELATED ACTIVITIES
    Russia; Law --Study and teaching--Russia (Federation); Legal services--Russia (Federation)
  - Tver State University (09850981), 1998 June 01-1998 September 30 (Reel R7736, Reel R8538)
    SUPPORT FOR A SUMMER SCHOOL FOR LAW STUDENT VOLUNTEERS
    Russia; Law --Study and teaching--Russia (Federation)
  - Twaweza Communications Limited (10301830), 2003 September 01-2005 August 31 (Reel R9073)
    For meetings and media campaigns to address concepts and definitions of leadership among the youth in Eastern Africa
    $212,500.00;$212,500.00
  - Twenty-First Century Foundation (09450883), 1994 July 01-1996 September 30 (Reel R7310)
    SUPPORT FOR STRATEGIC PLANNING PROCESS AND PUBLIC RELATIONS CAMPAIGN TARGETED TO AFRICAN AMERICAN DONORS
  - Twenty-First Century Foundation (09600470), 1996 March 01-1998 May 31 (Reel R7516)
    SUPPORT FOR IMPLEMENTATION OF STRATEGIC PLAN
  - Twenty-First Century Foundation (09901031), 1999 March 01-2003 December 31 (Reel R9215)
    SUPPORT FOR ITS PROGRAM TO STRENGTHEN AFRICAN AMERICAN PARTICIPATION AS DONORS AND ADVISORS TO ITS COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMS
    United States; Community development -- United States; African Americans -- Charities -- United States; Humanitarianism--United States
  - Twenty-First Century Foundation (10351161), 2003 May 01-2004 April 30 (Reel R9087)
    To establish a community asset fund in Greater Chicago
  - Twin Cities Public Television, Inc. (06000206), 1960 April 14-1963 April 30 (Reel R0211)
    DEVELOPMENT OF A SIX-STATE EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION NETWORK
  - Twin Cities Public Television, Inc. (06200442), 1962 August 17-1963 August 16 (Reel R0260)
    PRODUCTION OF EXEMPLARY LESSONS ON VIDEO TAPE
  - Twin Cities Public Television, Inc. (06600037), 1965 December 10-1971 June 09 (Reel R1470)
    GENERAL SUPPORT FOR COMMUNITY EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION STATIONS
    $373,778.00;$373,778.00
    Dressner, Howard R.
  - Twin Cities Public Television, Inc. (06800128), 1968 January 18-1978 January 17 (Reel R5655)
    MATCHING GENERAL SUPPORT GRANTS FOR COMMUNITY EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION STATIONS
    $84,832.00;$84,832.00
    Catalano, Richard M.
  - Twin Cities Public Television, Inc. (06800646), 1968 June 12-1978 June 11 (Reel R2735)
  - Twin Cities Public Television, Inc. (07800033), 1977 October 01-1978 September 30 (Reel R1412)
    GENERAL SUPPORT MATCHING GRANT TO IMPROVE LOCAL NEWS AND PUBLIC AFFAIRS PROGRAMMING
  - Twin Cities Public Television, Inc. (08450265), 1984 February 16-1984 August 15 (Reel R4422)
    SUPPORT FOR AN OUTREACH & AWARENESS CAMPAIGN TO BE CONDUCTED IN CONNECTION WITH THE AIRING OF "YOUR CHILDREN, OUR CHILDREN"
  - Twin Cities Public Television, Inc. (08700466), 1987 May 01-1989 February 28 (Reel R5599)
    SUPPORT FOR NEW PRODUCTIONS FOR ALIVE FROM OFF CENTER
  - Twin Cities Public Television, Inc. (09301493), 1993 September 01-1994 December 31 (Reel R7541)
    SUPPORT TO ALIVE TV FOR AN AUDIENCE RESEARCH INITIATIVE TO ENGAGE A YOUNGER AND MORE CULTURALLY DIVERSE AUDIENCE (008)
  - Twin Cities Rise! (09801630), 1998 August 01-2000 July 31 (Reel R8872)
    IMPLEMENTATION/EXPANSION OF AN INNOVATIVE WORKFORCE PROG. SERVING LOW-INCOME ADULTS IN MINNEAPOLIS, ST. PAUL, & NEIGHBORING SUBURBS
    United States; Economic development -- United States
  - Two Bridges Neighborhood Council, Inc. (06700427), 1967 July 14-1968 June 27 (Reel R2368)
    PLANNING OF AN EXPERIMENTAL SCHOOL UNIT FOR THE DEMONSTRATION PHASE OF THE DECENTRALIZATION PLAN OF THE BD. OF EDU. OF NY
  - Twyla Tharp Dance Foundation, Inc. (07900197), 1978 July 01-1983 June 30 (Reel R4605)
    $167,872.00;$138,404.00